A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, RG 1.30 (A2004) FA482
Rockefeller Archive Center
- AC.2004.028: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1994-2003; AC.2004.028; 7.86 Cubic Feet 6 standard record storage boxes, R3642-R3647.; 6 standard record storage boxes, R3642-R3647.
  - Equal Opportunity (EO), AC.2004.028.5; 5.24 Cubic Feet 4 record storage boxes
    - EO 9937 - UNITED WAY OF THE BAY AREA - SOLUTIONS: THE NEW FRONTIER OF ELECTRONIC DEMOCRACY, 1999-2002 (Box R3647)
    - EO 9943 - PUBLIC ADVOCATES - LATINO COALITION FOR A HEALTHY CALIFORNIA PROJECT, 1999-2004 (Box R3647)
  - Global Environment (GE), AC.2004.028.6; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - GE 9801 - ROCKEFELLER FOUNDATION - STRATEGIC PLANNING EXERCISE FOR GLOBAL ENVIRONMENT DIVISION, 1998-2000 (Box R3647)
      - Living on Earth, 2004.028.004; compact disc
    - GE 9804 - WORLD MEDIA FOUNDATION - ENERGY USE IN DEVELOPING WORLD RADIO SERIES, LIVING ON EARTH, 1997-2000 (Box R3647)
      - Threshold-Based Resource Management, 2004.028.003; floppy disk
    - GE 9806 - UNITED NATIONS ENVIRONMENT AND DEVELOPMENT - UNITEOD KINGDOM COMMITTEE (ENGLAND) - STAKEHOLDER TOOLKIT FOR WOMEN, 1998-2004 (Box R3647)
    - GE 9813 - BINGA TREES TRUST (ZIMBABWE) - MORINGA AND JATROPHA TREES PROJECTS, 1997-2001 (Box R3647)
    - GE 9815 - ARIAS FOUNDATION FOR PEACE AND HUMAN PROGRESS (COSTA RICA) - ENVIRONMENTAL SECURITY ON DEMOCRATIC GOVERNANCE IN GUATEMALA, 1998-2000 (Box R3647)
    - GE 9816 - FOUNDATION FOR BUSINESS AND SUSTAINABLE DEVELOPMENT (NORWAY) - ENERGY POLICY SCENARIO PROJECT, 1998-2003 (Box R3647)
    - GE 9902 - (GLOBAL ENVIRONMENT) - ENVIRONMENTAL SECURITY ON SUSTAINABLE AND ENRICHED LIVES, 1999-2000 (Box R3647)
- AC.2004.036: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1985-2003; AC.2004.036; 7.86 Cubic Feet 6 standard record storage boxes, R3648-R3653.; 6 standard record storage boxes, R3648-R3653.
  - GEE, AC.2004.036.1; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - GEE 9901 - INSTITUTE OF DEVELOPMENT STUDIES (ENGLAND) - 2000 INITIATIVE ON GLOBALIZATION, 1998-2000 (Box R3648)
  - Global Programs (GP), AC.2004.036.2; 2.63 Cubic Feet 2 record storage boxes
    - GP 9901 - UNIVERSITY OF COLORADO AT DENVER - LECTURES ON "THE PLANETARY INTEREST", 1999-2000 (Box R3648)
    - GP 9902 - UNITED NATIONS RESEACH INSTITUTE FOR SOCIAL DEVELOPMENT (SWITZERLAND) - TWO CONFERENCES ON NEO-LIBERALISM AND INSTITUTIONAL REFORM IN EAST ASIA, 1998-2001 (Box R3648)
    - GP 9905 - BENTON FOUNDATION - ONEWORLD WEB U.S., 1999-2000 (Box R3648)
    - GP 9907 - CENTER FOR STRATEGIC AND INTERNATIONAL STUDIES - EDUCATING CONGRESS ON INTERNATIONAL SECURITY, 1999-2003 (Box R3648)
    - GP 9909 - PUBLIC RADIO INTERNATIONAL - "THE WORLD", GLOBAL NEWS PROGRAM, 1999-2000 (Box R3648)
    - GP 9914 - CENTER FOR COMMUNITY ERVICE FUND - RESEARCH, REPORT AND CONFERENCE ON "DIGITAL DIVIDE", 1999-2000 (Box R3648)
    - GP 9917 - PROGRESSIVE (THE) - ITS MEDIA PROJECT, 1998-2001 (Box R3648)
    - GP 9919 - ASSOCIATION FOR PROGRESSIVE COMMUNICATIONS - "BEIJING + 5 IN AFRICA: WOMEN'S NGOS PARTICIPATING ONLINE", 1999-2002 (Box R3648)
    - GP 9920 - ASPEN INSTITUTE - CONFERENCE ON RELATIONSHIP BETWEEN BUSINESS AND SOCIETY, 1999-2000 (Box R3648)
    - GP 9921 - CIRCLE FOUNDATION - U.S. ATTITUDES ON GLOBALIZATION, 1999 (Box R3648)
    - GP 9923 - PLOUGHSHARES FUND - INFORMATION AND TECHNOLOGY PROJECT ON INTERNATIONAL SECURITY, 1999-2001 (Box R3648)
    - GP 9929 - CONSUMER FEDERATION OF AMERICA FOUNDATION - GLOBAL DIALOGUES ON PLANT BIOTECHNOLOGY, 1999-2001 (Box R3648)
    - GP 9930 - UNITED NATIONS FOUNDATION - CONFERENCE ON GLOBAL PUBLIC POLICY NETWORKS, 1999 (Box R3648)
    - RF 98028 #313; GP 9913 - INTERNATIONAL CENTER FOR GLOBAL COMMUNICATIONS FOUNDATION - MEDIA CHANNEL WEB SITE, 1998-2001 (Box R3648)
    - GP 9931 - MERIDIAN INSTITUTE - GLOBAL DIALOGUES ON PLANT BIOTECHNOLOGY, 1999-2000 (Box R3649)
    - GP 9932 - WORKSHOP UNLIMITED - ORGANIZATIONAL CHANGE IN NON-PROFIT ORGANIZATIONS, 1999-2002 (Box R3649)
    - GP 9933 - (GLOBAL PROGRAMS) - KASHMIR INITIATIVE, 1999-2000 (Box R3649)
    - GP 9934 - (GLOBAL PROGRAMS) - JAPANESE CONTEXT OF HUMAN AND TRADITIONALSECURITY INTERACTION, 1999 (Box R3649)
    - GP 9935 - INTERNATIONAL CENTRE FOR ETHNIC STUDIES (SRI LANKA) - COMMEMORATIVE PROGRAM FOR NEELAN TIRUCHELVAM, 1999-2001 (Box R3649)
    - GP 9937 - AMAZON CONSERVATION TEAM - BIOTECHNOLOGY REVOLUTION, 1999-2001 (Box R3649)
  - Health Sciences (HS), AC.2004.036.3; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - HS 9609 - CENTRE FOR DEVELOPMENT AND POPULATION ACTIVITIES - EVALUATION OF BETTER LIFE OPTION PROJECTS IN INDIA, 1996-2000 (Box R3649)
    - HS 9813 - WOMEN'S HEALTH PROJECT (SOUTH AFRICA) - GENDER AND REPRODUCTIVE HEALTH INITIATIVE, 1998-2001 (Box R3649)
    - HS 9904 - ROCKEFELLER FOUNDATION - NGO ACTIVITIES IN AFRICAN SCHOOL HEALTH PROGRAMS, 1998-2002 (Box R3649)
    - HS 9908 - JOHNS HOPKINS UNIVERSITY - HEALTH EQUITY IN NEPAL, 1999-2002 (Box R3649)
    - HS 9911 - MCMASTER UNIVERSITY (CANADA) - TWO WORKSHOPS ON WOMEN, HIV/AIDS AND VIOLENCE, 1999-2001 (Box R3649)
    - HS 9917 - SUDDEN INFANT DEATH SYNDROME ALLIANCE - EDUCATIONAL MATERIALS TO DECREASE SYNDROME, 1999-2001 (Box R3649)
  - International Security (IS), AC.2004.036.4; 2.63 Cubic Feet 2 record storage boxes
    - IS 9526 - UNIVERSITY OF CALIFORNIA (SAN DIEGO) - COMPARATIVE REGIONAL APPORACHES TO NUCLEAR NONPROLIFERATION, 1995-2002 (Box R3649)
    - IS 9828 - FEDERATION OF AMERICAN SCIENTISTS FUND - PUBLIC EYE WORK FOCUSED ON NORTH KOREA, 1998-2001 (Box R3649)
    - IS 9907 - CARNEGIE MELLON UNIVERSITY - HIGH TECHNOLOGIES FOR SUSTAINABLE ENERGY IN INDIA TO COUNTER NUCLEARIZATION, 1997-1999 (Box R3649)
    - IS 9909 - COLUMBIA UNIVERSITY - GULF/2000 PROJECT, 1994-2003 (Box R3649)
    - IS 9913 - VIETNAM VETERANS OF AMERICA FOUNDATION - DEMINING INITIATIVE, 1998-2000 (Box R3650)
    - IS 9916 - NATIONAL ACADEMY OF SCIENCES - U.S.-INDIA NUCLEAR DIALOGUE, 1999-2000 (Box R3650)
    - IS 9919 - NAUTILUS OF AMERICA - SOUTH ASIA PEACE AND SECURITY NETWORK, 1999 (Box R3650)
  - Population Sciences (PS), AC.2004.036.5; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - PS 9617 - UNIVERSITY OF COSTA RICA - 1984-1995 EFFECTS OF POPULATION GROWTH ON COSTA RICAN FORESTS, 1996-2000 (Box R3650)
    - PS 9702 - FOX, MICHAEL P. - PRIVATE SECTOR AND SOUTH-SOUTH REPRODUCTIVE HEALTH, 1997-1999 (Box R3650)
    - PS 9715 - SAI, FRED T. - GHANAIANS VIEWS ON REPRODUCTIVE HEALTH AND FAMILY LIFE ISSUES, 1997-2001 (Box R3650)
    - PS 9813 - COLLEGE DE FRANCE - COLLOQUIUM ON POPULATION DYNAMICS IN INDUSTRIALIZED COUNTRIES, 1998-1999 (Box R3650)
    - PS 9814 - PEKING UNION MEDICAL COLLEGE (CHINA) - EPIDIDYMAL SPERM MATURATION STUDY, 1998-2001 (Box R3650)
    - PS 9820 - MEXICAN FAMILY PLANNING ASSOCIATION (MEXICO) - SOUTH-SOUTH NGO COOPERATION, 1998-2000 (Box R3650)
    - PS 9903 - UNIVERSITY OF CHILE - CORPUS LUTEUM RESEARCH, 1998-2000 (Box R3650)
    - PS 9913 - POPULATION COUNCIL - SOUTH AFRICA CONFERENCE ON ABORTION LAW, 1999-2001 (Box R3650)
  - Special Interests (SI), AC.2004.036.6; 2.63 Cubic Feet 2 record storage boxes
    - Sl 9718 - COUNCIL ON FOUNDATIONS - COMMUNICATI ONS/LEGISLATIVE INITIATIVE, 1997-2002 (Box R3650)
    - Sl 9722 - CONSUMERS UNION OF UNITED STATES, INC. - EDUCATIONAL ASSETS PROJECT, 1997-2000 (Box R3650)
    - Sl 9803 - TENGBOCHE MONASTERY (NEPAL) - ECO-CENTER FOR INFORMATION AND EDUCATION ON SUSTAINABILITY, 1997-2002 (Box R3650)
    - SI 9804 - ARIZONA STATE UNIVERSITY - "1848/1898@1998: TRANS HISTORIC THRESHOLDS", 1997-2003 (Box R3650)
      Special format items (audio, film, video, digital media, library materials, memorabilia, oversize, and photographic material) have been separated from the file and assigned a unique separation number, as noted. Requests to access open special formats should reference the unique separation number.
      - Transhistoric Thresholds Conference, 1998; 2004.036.003; compact disc
    - SI 9812 - ADVERTISI NG COUNCIL - COMMITMENT 2000 PROJECT, 1998-1999 (Box R3651)
    - SI 9814 - HUNTER COLLEGE OF THE CITY UNIVERSITY OF NEW YORK - "HISTORICAL ARCHIVES OF PUERTO RICAN MIGRATION TO U.S." PROJECT, 1997-2000 (Box R3651)
      - [untitled], 2004.036.004; floppy disk
    - SI 9907 - NATIONAL NETWORK OF G?RANTMAKERS - STUDY ON BOARD AND STAFF DIVERSITY IN PHILANTHROPY, 1997-2001 (Box R3651)
    - SI 9910 - INDEPENDENT SECTOR - BUILDING CAPACITY PORTION OF PUBLIC POLICY INITIATIVE, 1999-2000 (Box R3651)
    - SI 9911 - VIDEAZIMUT (CANADA) - TRAINING EVALUATION AND NEEDS ASSESSMENT PROGRAM, 1999-2000 (Box R3651)
    - SI 9912 - NONPROFIT COORDINATING COMMITTEE OF NEW YORK - 1990 STUDY OF NYC'S NONPROFIT SECTOR, 1999-2004 (Box R3651)
    - SI 9913 - ASHOKA: INNOVATORS FOR THE PUBLIC - CHANGEMAKERS' MEDIA PROJECT, 1997-2001 (Box R3651)
    - SI 9916 - IMAGINARIO (COLOMBIA) - DOCUMENTARY ON PEACE INITIATIVE, 1999-2000 (Box R3651)
    - SI 9918 - SAN ANTONIO AREA FOUNDATION - COMMUNITY TECHNOLOGY RESOURCE CENTER, 1999-2001 (Box R3651)
  - Rockefeller Foundation (RF), AC.2004.036.7; 2.63 Cubic Feet 2 record storage boxes
    - RF 91038 - NEW YORK UNIVERSITY - ARMSWATCH, 1990-1997; 2 folders. (Box R3652)
    - RF 91038 - NEW YORK UNIVERSITY - ARMSWATCH - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL, 1990-1997; 2 folders. (Box R3652)
    - RF 91083 - POPULATION SCIENCES - SUB-SAHARAN AFRICA RESEARCH AND TRAINING, 1985-1992; 2 folders. (Box R3652, Box R3653)
    - RF 91083- POPULATION SCIENCES - SUB-SAHARAN AFRICA RESEARCH AND TRAINING - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL, 1985-1992 (Box R3652, Box R3653)
      - Diskette for AFROP Report Bud Harkovy, 1991; 2004.036.001; floppy disk
      - Rockefeller foundation reviews, 2004.036.002; floppy disk
    - RF 92087 - CONTRACEPTIVE INTRODUCTION PROJECTS, 1991-1994 (Box R3653)
    - RF 92092 #74 - UGANDA - HEALTH (MINISTRY OF) - IXTH INTERNATIONAL CONFERENCE ON AIDS AND STDs IN AFRICA, 1994-2001 (Box R3653)
    - RF 92053 - (STRENGTHENING CHINESE UNIVERSITIES) - PILOT FELLOWSHIP PROGRAM, 1991-2000; 2 folders. (Box R3653)
- AC.2004.045: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1984-2003; AC.2004.045; 14.41 Cubic Feet 11 standard record storage boxes, R3654-R3664.; 11 standard record storage boxes, R3654-R3664.
  - Rockefeller Foundation (RF), AC.2004.045.1; 14.41 Cubic Feet 11 record storage boxes
    - RF 93022 #224 - BOGOR AGRICULTURAL UNIVERSITY (INDONESIA) - BIOTECHNOLOGY CAREER FELLOWSHIP FOR RATNA HADIOETOMO, 1996-2002 (Box R3654)
    - RF 93022 #227 - DENG ZIXIN, 1991-2001 (Box R3654)
    - RF 93028 #15 - UNIVERSITY OF PENNSYLVANIA - MALAWI NURSE - MIDWIVES TRAINING, 1989-2000 (Box R3654)
    - RF 93039 - (BELLAGIO POPULATION AND DEVELOPMENT FORUM), 1993-1999; 2 folders. (Box R3655, Box R3654)
    - RF 93039 - (BELLAGIO POPULATION AND DEVELOPMENT FORUM) - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL, 1993-1999; 5 folders. (Box R3655, Box R3654)
      Special format items (audio, film, video, digital media, library materials, memorabilia, oversize, and photographic material) have been separated from the file and assigned a unique separation number, as noted. Requests to access open special formats should reference the unique separation number
      - Resource Mobilization Strategy on Population, 1993; 2004.045.001; floppy disk (Box R3655)
    - RF 93045 #15 - CHRISTIAN MEDICAL COLLEGE (INDIA) - SEXUAL BEHAVIOR AND PRACTICES OF ADOLESCENTS IN TAMIL NADU, INDIA, 1995-2000 (Box R3656)
    - RF 93063 #78 - ALL INDIA INSTITUTE OF MEDICAL SCIENCES - HORMONAL REGULATION OF SERTOLI PROTEINS IN RATS, 1994-2000 (Box R3656)
    - RF 94010 #547 - UNIVERSITY OF THE STATE OF CAMPINAS (BRAZIL) - RESIDENT FELLOWSHIPS - CULTURE AND POLITICS PROGRAM, 1993-2001 (Box R3656)
    - RF 94010 #547 - UNIVERSITY OF THE STATE OF CAMPINAS (BRAZIL) - RESIDENT FELLOWSHIPS - CULTURE AND POLITICS PROGRAM - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL, 1993-2001 (Box R3656)
    - RF 94010 #550 - UNIVERSITY OF CALIFORNIA (LOS ANGELES) - ESTABLISH INSTITUTE FOR STUDY OF GENDER IN AFRICA, 1994-2001 (Box R3656)
    - RF 94010 #560 - FEDERAL UNIVERSITY OF MINAS GERAIS - "LATE MODERNITIES IN BRAZIL" PROJECT, 1995-2000; 2 folders. (Box R3657)
    - RF 94010 #560 - FEDERAL UNIVERSITY OF MINAS GERAIS - "LATE MODERNITIES IN BRAZIL" PROJECT - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL, 1995-2000; 2 folders. (Box R3657)
    - RF 94014 - (INTERDISCIPLINARY ARTISTS PROGRAM), 1984-1997; 3 folders. (Box R3658, Box R3657, Box R3659)
    - RF 94014 - (INTERDISCIPLINARY ARTISTS PROGRAM) - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL, 1984-1997; 5 folders. (Box R3658, Box R3657, Box R3659)
    - RF 94024 #87 - LONDON SCHOOL OF HYGIENE AND TROPICAL MEDICINE (ENGLAND) - HIV/AIDS IN ABIDJAN, IVORY COAST, 1993-2002 (Box R3659)
    - RF 94027 #603 - NJOYA, ABOUBAKAR - ACA: CATTLE PRODUCTIVITY IN A SUSTAINABLE AGRICULTURE IN CAMEROON, 1996-2002 (Box R3659)
    - RF 94027 #627 - LEBBIE, AIAH RANDOLPH - ADIA: NON-TIMBER FOREST PRODUCTS IN WEST AFRICA, 1996-1999 (Box R3659)
    - RF 94038 #14 - ESQUEL-ECUADOR FOUNDATION - PROGRAM TO PROMOTE LOCAL PHILANTHROPY, 1995-2001; 2 folders. (Box R3659)
    - RF 94052 - (NATIONAL EPIDEMIOLOGY BOARDS), 1993-2000 (Box R3660)
    - RF 94054 #19 - LONDON SCHOOL OF HYGIENE AND TROPICAL MEDICINE - REPRODUCTIVE HEALTH RESEARCH IN SOUTH ASIA, 1994-2003 (Box R3660)
    - RF 94054 #21 - TATA INSTITUTE OF SOCIAL SCIENCES (INDIA) - SEXUALITY AMONG URBAN COLLEGE STUDENTS, 1995-2001 (Box R3660)
    - RF 94055 #17 - SOCIETY FOR DEVELOPMENT ALTERNATIVES (INDIA) - MICRO-ENTERPRISES BASED ON ENERGY-SAVING TECHNOLOGIES, 1994-2001 (Box R3660)
    - RF 94057 #64 - HANDSPRING TRUST FOR PUPPETRY IN EDUCATION (SOUTH AFRICA) - VIDEO FOR SCIENCE TEACHERS OF PRIMARY SCHOOL, 1995-1998 (Box R3660)
    - RF 94063 #13 - HARVARD UNIVERSITY - CONFERENCE ON URBAN POVERTY AND SOCIAL EXCLUSION, 1996-2001 (Box R3660)
    - RF 95001 #352 - UNIVERSITY OF TOKYO (JAPAN) - SUBMERGENCE TOLERANCE IN RICE, 1995-2000 (Box R3660)
    - RF 95003 #565 - YALE UNIVERSITY - THIRD WORLD MODERNIZATION, 1988-2000; 6 folders. (Box R3661)
    - RF 95003 #566 - GRADUATE SCHOOL AND UNIVERSITY CENTER OF THE CITY UNIVERSITY OF NEW YORK - RESIDENT FELLOWS CENTER FOR LESBIAN AND GAY STUDIES, 1992-2003 (Box R3662)
    - RF 95003 #567 - UNIVERSITY OF TORONTO (CANADA) - RESIDENT FELLOWS (CENTRE FOR THE STUDY OF RELIGION), 1996-2000 (Box R3662)
    - RF 95003 #570 - INSTITUTE FOR THE STUDY OF RELIGION (BRAZIL) - RESIDENT FELLOWSHIPS, 1995-2000 (Box R3662)
    - RF 95003 #572 - LA MORADA CORPORATION FOR THE DEVELOPMENT OF WOMEN (CHILE) ú RESIDENT FELLOWSHIPS, 1996-2000; 2 folders. (Box R3662)
    - RF 95020 #105 - UGANDA VIRUS RESEARCH INSTITUTE - STD CONTROL AND PREVENTION - RAKAI PROJECT, 1993-1998 (Box R3663)
    - RF 95022 #661 - MBILA, MONDAY OCHU - ADIA: DISTRIBUTION AND MOVEMENT OF HEAVY METALS IN SEWAGE-SLUDGE-AMENDED NIGERIAN SOIL, 1996-2002 (Box R3663)
    - RF 95022 #686 - ABDELKADIR, ABDU - ACA: AGROFORESTRY SYSTEMS IN DRY AREAS OF ETHIOPIA, 1997-2002 (Box R3663)
    - RF 95022 #687 - MUGANGU, TRINTO E. - ACA: GORILLA CONSERVATION IN CONGO, 1997-2002 (Box R3663)
    - RF 95022 #692 - MASINYANDIMA, MUTSA - ADIA: LAND USE CHANGE ON RECHARGE AND WATER RESOURCES IN WEST AFRICA, 1997-2003 (Box R3663)
    - RF 95022 #694 - NZIMA, MUNTUBANI D.S. - ACA: DEVELOPMENT OF A TRUE POTATO SEED TECHNOLOGY IN ZIMBABWE, 1997-2002 (Box R3663)
    - RF 95024 #256 - PRINCETON BALLET SOCIETY - MULTl-MEDIA DANCE AND FILM PROJECT "LOS PELEGRINOS", 1996-2002 (Box R3663)
    - RF 95027 #141 - INDOCHINA ARTS PROJECT - "FIVE PILLARS" EXHIBITION, 1995-1998 (Box R3663)
    - RF 95037 #3 - SONGA, JOSEPHINE M. - STEMBORERS IN MAIZE PRODUCTION OF EASTERN KENYA, 1995-2001 (Box R3663)
    - RF 95040 #73 - UNIVERSITY OF SWAZILAND - LINKING SCIENCE EDUCATION IN SCHOOLS WITH LOCAL INDUSTRY AND TECHNOLOGY, 1995-2002 (Box R3663)
    - RF 95043 #31 - RANFURLY LIBRARY SERVICE - PUBLISHERS' RESOURCE PACK PROJECT, 1992-2000 (Box R3663)
    - RF 95046 #2 - STANFORD UNIVERSITY - PATENT ISSUES RELATED TO RICE BIOTECHNOLOGY PROGRAM, 1994-2001 (Box R3663)
    - RF 95046 #8 - NATIONAL CENTER FOR GENETIC ENGINEERING AND BIOTECHNOLOGY (THAILAND) - GENETICALLY ENGINEERED CROP PLANTS FACILITY, 1997-2000 (Box R3663)
    - RF 95047 #38 - MAULANA AZAD MEDICAL COLLEGE - REPRODUCTIVE TRACT INFECTIONS/SEXUALLY-TRANSMITTED DISEASES AND WOMEN IN URBAN SLUM OF NEW DELHI, 1995-2001 (Box R3663)
    - RF 95050 #101 - DEMBELE, MARTIAL - PROFESSIONAL DEVELOPMENT OF PRIMARY SCHOOL TEACHERS IN BURKINA FASO, 1996-2002 (Box R3664)
    - RF 95050 #104 - MBUGUA, JUSTINA TATA - EDUCATIONAL RESOURCES OF WOMEN IN KENYA, 1996-2004 (Box R3664)
    - RF 95050 #93 - UNIVERSITY OF MALAWI - SCHOOL DROPOUT AMONG BOYS AND GIRLS IN PRIMARY SCHOOLS, 1996-2000 (Box R3664)
    - RF 96001 #400 - UNIVERSITY OF DHAKA (BANGLADESH) - FLOODING-TOLERANT RICE CULTIVARS, 1995-2000 (Box R3664)
    - RF 96001 #432 - NATIONAL AGRICULTURAL SCIENCE AND TECHNOLOGY INSTITUTE (KOREA) - XANTHOMONAS ORYZAE PV. ORYZAE FELLOWSHIP, 1996-2001 (Box R3664)
    - RF 96001 #433 - PUNJAB AGRICULTURAL UNIVERSITY (INDIA) - GENETIC TRANSFORMATION OF BASMATI RICE FELLOWSHIP, 1996-2001 (Box R3664)
    - RF 96001 #460 - INTERNATIONAL RICE RESEARCH INSTITUTE - RICE RESEARCH PRIORITIZATION, 1992-2000 (Box R3664)
    - RF 96001 #462 - ZHEJIANG AGRICULTURAL UNIVERSITY (CHINA) - BIOTECHNOLOGY CAREER FELLOWSHIP FOR WU PING, 1996-2001 (Box R3664)
    - RF 96001 #463 - VIRGINIA POLYTECHNIC INSTITUTE AND STATE UNIVERSITY - APPLICATION RFLP MAPPING TO HYBRID RICE BREEDING, 1992-2000 (Box R3664)
    - RF 96001 #493 - MYONG JI UNIVERSITY (KOREA) - BIOTECHNOLOGY CAREER FELLOWSHIP FOR KIM JU-KON, 1996-2001 (Box R3664)
    - RF 96003 #574 - NEW YORK UNIVERSITY - RESIDENT FELLOWSHIPS (INTERNATIONAL CENTER FOR ADVANCED STUDIES), 1996-2000 (Box R3664)
- AC.2004.048: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1993-2003; AC.2004.048; 5.24 Cubic Feet 4 standard record storage boxes, R3665-R3668.; 4 standard record storage boxes, R3665-R3668.
  - Rockefeller Foundation (RF), AC.2004.048.1; 5.24 Cubic Feet 4 record storage boxes
    - RF 96006 #14 - PURDUE UNIVERSITY - STRIGA RESISTANCE IN AFRICAN MAIZE, 1997-2002 (Box R3665)
    - RF 96008 #83 - MAKERERE UNIVERSITY (UGANDA) - AGRICULTURAL PLANT RESIDUES AND SUSTAINABLE DEVELOPMENT, 1992-2002 (Box R3665)
    - RF 96008 #86 - UNIVERSITY OF MALAWI - BUNDA COLLEGE OF AGRICULTURE - GRAIN-LEGUME SUBSECTOR, 1996-2002 (Box R3665)
    - RF 96020 #65 - RUSH-PRESBYTERIAN-ST. LUKE'S MEDICAL CENTER - VAGINAL CONTRACEPTIVES, 1993-2002 (Box R3665)
    - RF 96020 #73 - OTTAWA CIVIC HOSPITAL LOEB RESEARCH INSTITUTE (CANADA) - SPERM SURFACE PROTEINS, 1998-1999 (Box R3665)
    - RF 96022 #722 - MUKISIRA, EPHRAIM AMIANI - ACA: FEED TECHOLOGIES FOR IMPROVED SMALLHOLDER DAIRY PRODUCTION IN KENYA, 1997-2002 (Box R3665)
    - RF 96022 #723 - SOCIAL SCIENCE RESEARCH COUNCIL - RATE OF RETURN TO AFRICA OF AFRICANS EARNING PH.D.'S, 1997-2002 (Box R3665)
    - RF 96022 #724 - ASSOCIATION OF AFRICAN UNIVERSITIES (GHANA) - GENDER PROGRAMS AND AFFIRMATIVE ACTION INITIATIVES IN AFRICAN HIGHER EDUCATION, 1997-2001 (Box R3665)
    - RF 96022 #729 - NASINYAMA, GEORGE WILLIAM - ACA: SALMONELLA INFECTION IN POULTRY IN UGANDA, 1997-2002 (Box R3665)
    - RF 96022 #731 - KABAGAMBE, EDMOND - ADIA: A SURVEY OF HEALTH MANAGEMENT-GOAT DISEASES IN UGANDA, 1997-2001 (Box R3665)
    - RF 96022 #733 - SOCIAL SCIENCE RESEARCH COUNCIL - WORKSHOPS ON CROSS-REGIONAL RESEARCH NETWORKS IN AFRICA, 1997-2002 (Box R3665)
    - RF 96023 #242 - RF 96023 #242 - UNIVERSITY OF CALIFORNIA (LOS ANGELES) - "THE VIETNAM SERIES", 1996-2003 (Box R3666)
    - RF 96022 #738 - HAKIZA, JOHN JOHNSON - ACA: POTATO TECHNOLOGY IN UGANDA, 1997-2002 (Box R3666)
    - RF 96022 #739 - ZINNAH, MOSES MOROE - ACA: AGRICULTURAL EDUCATION AT TERTIARY INSTITUTIONS IN GHANA, 1997-2000 (Box R3666)
    - RF 96022 #751 - DRAMMEH, BAKARY S. - ADIA: "COMPARISON OF SOLAR-DRIED MANGOES AND HIGH DOSE VITAMIN A IN GAMBIAN CHILDREN", 1998-2002 (Box R3666)
    - RF 96022 #754 - TANGKA, FLORENCE - ADIA: "CROSS-BRED COWS AND FOOD SECURITY IN ETHIOPIA", 1997-2002 (Box R3666)
    - RF 96022 #756 - YNTISO, GEBRE D. - ADIA: POPULATION DISPLACEMENT AND FOOD SECURITY IN ETHIOPIA, 1997-2001 (Box R3666)
    - RF 96022 #781 - MUNISHI, PANTALEO K. T. - ADIA: NATURAL FOREST ECOSYSTEMS IN TANZANIA, 1998-2002 (Box R3666)
    - RF 96022 #785 - YASINDI, ANDREW WAMALWA - ADIA: ECOLOGY OF CILIATES IN THREE EAST AFRICAN LAKES, 1998-2002 (Box R3666)
    - RF 96022 #787 - ASFAW, SOSINA B. - ADIA: BORANA PASTORALISM AND BUSH ENCROACHMENT IN ETHIOPIA, 1998-2000 (Box R3666)
    - RF 96022 #789 - HAILE MARIAM, DAMEN - ACA: SOCIAL INSURANCE AND HEALTH CARE IN ETHIOPIA, 1998-2001 (Box R3666)
    - RF 96022 #791 - ALLEN, WILLIAM E. - ADIA: LIBERIAN COASTAL ENCLAVES AND THE FRONTIER IN THE NINETEENTH CENTURY, 1998-2003 (Box R3666)
    - RF 96024 #281 - NEW YORK THEATRE WORKSHOP - NEW PRODUCTION WITH GRUPO DE TEATRO MACUNAIMA, 1997-2000 (Box R3666)
    - RF 96024 #301 - BANG ON A CAN - BALINESE THEMED SHADOW PUPPET/MUSICAL WORK, 1997-2002 (Box R3666)
    - RF 96035 #504 - HANOI MEDICAL COLLEGE (VIETNAM) - CLINICAL EPIDEMIOLOGY AND PUBLIC HEALTH, 1996-1998 (Box R3666)
    - RF 96041 #53 - INTERNATIONAL COUNCIL OF MUSEUMS (FRANCE) - WORKSHOP ON ILLEGAL TRAFFIC IN ARABIC CULTURAL PROPERTY, 1998-2000 (Box R3666)
    - RF 96047 #103 - SERVICIOS PARA EL DESARROLLO, AC. (MEXICO) - NATURAL RESOURCES MANAGEMENT IN THE VALLEY OF MEZQUITAL, 1993-2003 (Box R3667)
    - RF 96047 #106 - UNIVERSIDAD AUTONOMA CHAPINGO (MEXICO) - SUSTAINABLE DEVELOPMENT IN SINALOA, 1993-2002 (Box R3667)
    - RF 96047 #107 - PROYECTO SIERRA DE SANTA MARTA, AC. (MEXICO) - "PARTICIPATIVE PLANNING AND SUSTAINABLE DEVELOPMENT OF THE TEXIZAPAN - ZONUAPA WATERSHED", 1994-2001 (Box R3667)
    - RF 96047 #108 - ESTUDIOS RURALES Y ASESORIA, AC. (MEXICO) - ENVIRONMENT MANAGEMENT IN ZAPOTECO AND CHINANTECA, 1993-2000 (Box R3667)
    - RF 96047 #109 - COLEGIO DE POSTGRADUADOS (MEXICO) - NATURAL RESOURCES MANAGEMENT IN WETLANDS, 1993-2002 (Box R3667)
    - RF 96047 #110 - MADERAS DEL PUEBLO DEL SURESTE, AC. (MEXICO) - DEVELOPMENT AND COMMUNITY PARTICIPATION IN CHIMALAPAS, 1993-2001 (Box R3667)
    - RF 96047 #111 - UNIVERSIDAD AUTONOMA DE YUCATAN (MEXICO) - DEVELOPMENT OF DEPT. OF MANAGEMENT AND CONSERVATION OF TROPICAL NATURAL RESOURCES, 1995-2002 (Box R3667)
    - RF 96047 #117 - VICENTE GUERRERO RURAL DEVELOPMENT PROJECT - PEASANT TO PEASANT PROGRAM, 1997-2002 (Box R3668)
    - RF 96048 #49 - COMMITTEE FOR STUDIES ON WOMEN, FAMILY AND ENVIRONMENT IN AFRICA (SENEGAL) - INTERGENERATIONAL COMMUNICATION ON REPRODUCTIVE ISSUES, 1996-2001 (Box R3668)
    - RF 96048 #60 - UNIVERSITY OF OUAGADOUGOU (BURKINA FASO) - ADOLESCENT SEXUALITY AND HIV/AIDS IN BURKINA FASO, 1998-2001 (Box R3668)
    - RF 96055 #5 - ARMENIAN NATIONAL INSTITUTE - GATHERING ARMENIAN-RELATED MATERIALS FOR EXHIBITION, 1999-2000 (Box R3668)
    - RF 96057 #41 - SITKA TRIBE OF ALASKA - "HEALING HEART TOTEM POLE" PROJECT, 1997-2000 (Box R3668)
    - RF 96057 #52 - CENTER FOR ARTS CRITICISM - MULTIMEDIA PROGRAM, "LA FAMILIA", 1998-2002 (Box R3668)
    - RF 96057 #54 - EAST BAY INSTITUTE FOR URBAN ARTS - TRAINING PROGRAM FOR OAKLAND YOUTH, "IMAGES CREATING UNITY", 1998-2004 (Box R3668)
    - RF 97001 #517 - INDIAN INSTITUTE OF TECHNOLOGY - BIOTECHNOLOGY CAREER FELLOWSHIP FOR DEBRABATA BASU, 1997-2000 (Box R3668)
    - RF 97001 #521 - UNIVERSITY OF MADRAS (INDIA) - BIOTECHNOLOGY CAREER FELLOWSHIP FOR S. S. GNANAMANICKAM, 1997-2001 (Box R3668)
- AC.2004.053: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1993-2002; AC.2004.053; 2.63 Cubic Feet 2 standard record storage boxes, R3669, R3670; 2 standard record storage boxes, R3669, R3670
  - Rockefeller Foundation (RF), AC.2004.053.1; 2.63 Cubic Feet 2 record storage boxes
    - RF 97001 #527 - CHINA NATIONAL RICE RESEARCH INSTITUTE - RICE BLAST FUNGUS, 1996-2001 (Box R3669)
    - RF 97001 #528 - PONDICHERRY UNIVERSITY (INDIA) - BIOTECHNOLOGY CAREER FELLOWSHIP FOR NATARAJAN SAKTHIVEL, 1997-2000 (Box R3669)